module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'Which of these inventions was NOT showcased at the 1893 Chicago World\'s Fair',
    a: 'Hair Dryer',
    b: 'Spray Paint',
    c: 'Dishwasher',
    d: 'Pabst Blue Ribbon',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the largest living carnivore?',
    a: 'Hippo',
    b: 'Grizzly Bear',
    c: 'Great White Shark',
    d: 'Elephant Seal',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'How much money does an US Olympic Gold Medal winner get?',
    a: '$10k',
    b: '$25k',
    c: '$50k',
    d: '$75k',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What movie was called "Run! Run! CLOUDZILLA!" in China?',
    a: 'Cloudy With a Chance of Meatballs',
    b: 'The Mist',
    c: 'Twister',
    d: 'Sharknado',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'In what key do houseflies hum?',
    a: 'D',
    b: 'E',
    c: 'F',
    d: 'G',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the best selling Nintendo game of all time?',
    a: 'Super Mario Bros',
    b: 'Wii Sports',
    c: 'Mario Kart',
    d: 'Legend of Zelda',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What does the X in X-Men stand for?',
    a: 'Professor X',
    b: 'Exceptional',
    c: 'Extreme',
    d: 'Extra',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'What group of animals is officially called an "Army"?',
    a: 'Caterpillars',
    b: 'Ants',
    c: 'Wombats',
    d: 'Mice',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What has the highest pH level?',
    a: 'Vinegar',
    b: 'Water',
    c: 'Lemon Juice',
    d: 'Orange Juice',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who coined the term "White House"?',
    a: 'Abraham Lincoln',
    b: 'Benjamin Franklin',
    c: 'Teddy Roosevelt',
    d: 'Grover Cleveland',
    answer: 'c'
  },
];
